Shakin'!
Nighttime and Idol
Well, here we are at the end of "Nighttime and Idols".
May I ask Ueda-san to make an announcement?
Yes, I do. On Saturday, July 8th, we, X Shoujo-tai, will be holding our 8th anniversary live at Canal City Theater in Fukuoka.
Our 8th anniversary!
It's finally our 8th anniversary. It will be our first time to perform at the Canal City Theater,
It's the 5th anniversary of this x girl group, so I hope many of you will come to celebrate with us.
I see. I have an image of Canal City Theater as something happening at Canal City,
At the Fountain Square,
Yes, that's right. I have an image that they often do something like that,
It used to be a theater for theater companies,
It used to be a theater for theater companies, but recently it has been used for live performances as well.
I see.
Yes, I do. I will be happy to do it.
And now..,
And from Thursday, July 13th to Sunday, July 16th, I will be performing at Japan Expo Paris 2023 in Paris, France.
You will be in Paris in five days?
I'll be in Paris in 5 days?
That's great.
I can't imagine it, but even I can't imagine it. I didn't think I would be going to Paris.
This Japan Expo is a lot of fun, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Have you been there before?
In Thailand.
Yes, I've been to Thailand.
It's nice.
This is my first time in Europe.
By all means, please go to France and show the people in Europe who like Japanese culture.
I can show them the charm of Japan and Kyushu.
The charm of Kyushu.
Yes, I will do my best. I will do my best.
That's good.
And..,
Batten! Music Day, we will be holding "Request Live" at ZEPP in Tohoku.
ZEPP Fukuoka will be held on Friday, August 11, a national holiday, and ZEPP Diversity will be held on Sunday, August 20.
We will be performing a set list based on the songs that you have requested,
Some of the songs will be performed as a band set,
What?
Yes, it will be a special concert. I think it will be a special live performance.
Please come and join us on the day of music.
You are already getting requests, aren't you?
That's right. So I think you may be able to see some songs that are not often performed.
Please look forward to it.
And, yes,
Yes. And we also have a year-end live concert scheduled,
It will be held on Sunday, December 17 at Tokyo Dome City Hall.
Oh!
We have been working as Batten Shoujo-tai with the goal of filling Nakano Sunplaza to capacity in 2022,
This year, we would like to do our best to fill the Tokyo Dome City Hall to capacity of 3,000.
Tokyo Dome City has a capacity of 3,000?
Yes, that's great!
The end of the year sounds great.
I would like to make it a live concert that even those who have never seen Batten Shoujo-tai perform can enjoy,
So please come and enjoy the show.
Please come and enjoy the show,
I would like to thank Mr. Ueda, who is such an energetic Wagashoku-chan,
I would like to present you with a present from Yasan-kun, a tea that will cheer you up.
This time, the tea is Chirancha from Kagoshima.
Kagoshima.
Tea.
Looks delicious.
I will have it.
Please drink it.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It has bitterness, but it's easy to drink.
It's really delicious. It makes me feel warm.
It cheered me up.
Now then, I hope you will close this program in a cute way.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching Night and Idol.
We, x girl squad, are always looking forward to seeing you at our live shows, so please come and see us.
This is Riko Ueda of x girl group.
This program was provided by Mohi-san, Atmaruku Fukubaya-san, Yuukiku-san, Kou-tachi, and Kohi-san.
Thank you very much.